<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HarmonyCare</string>
    <string name="title_checklist">Checklist</string>
    <string name="title_record">Record</string>
    <string name="title_pattern">Pattern</string>
    <string name="title_community">Community</string>
    <string name="title_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="google_server_client_id">185976520158-phphtutm302clototd3rqgecng4a4bg2.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>

    <string-array name="weight_array">
        <item>49~60cm</item>
        <item>52~65cm</item>
        <item>56~68cm</item>
        <item>59~70cm</item>
        <item>60~72cm</item>
        <item>62~74cm</item>
        <item>64~76cm</item>
        <item>65~77cm</item>
        <item>67~79cm</item>
        <item>68~79cm</item>
        <item>72~80cm</item>
        <item>73~81cm</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="height_array">
        <item>3~5.7kg</item>
        <item>3.9~7.4kg</item>
        <item>5~8.4kg</item>
        <item>5.6~9.2kg</item>
        <item>5.9kg~9.6kg</item>
        <item>6.2~10kg</item>
        <item>6.6~11kg</item>
        <item>6.8~11kg</item>
        <item>7~11.4kg</item>
        <item>7.4~11kg</item>
        <item>8~11kg</item>
        <item>8.8~12kg</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="growth_array">
        <item>"Distinguish between mother's voice.
Watch the toy move.
My limbs are active."
</item>
        <item>"I smile at my mom’s face.
Stretch out your arms and legs.
I also lie down and lift my chest.
Start babbling."</item>
        <item>"Clear your own throat.
It reacts to sounds and smells.
Blink your eyes.
Suck your finger.
Waving my arms and kicking"</item>
        <item>"My hair becomes stronger.
You can extend your arms and grab moving objects.
Responds to colored toys.
I can tell my mom’s emotional changes.
The baby's emotional expression also becomes richer."</item>
        <item>"My hair is falling out.
Neck movement becomes more active.
As your eyesight develops, you become more interested in objects.
They put everything they see into their mouths.
You can rock your body left and right and flip over."</item>
        <item>"Teeth are starting to grow.
You can lie down and roll over.
Sit down, extend your arms in the air, and pull them back.
He tries to hold the toy in both hands, but keeps losing it."</item>
        <item>"When teething, you bite your fingers.
Their memory develops, allowing them to explore hidden objects and imitate their mother's actions.
You can sit alone.
It is good to be careful about cavities and prevent mouth shape deformation."</item>
        <item>"I pick up and eat food alone.
You can move objects from hand to hand.
Since separation anxiety appears and the child does not want to be separated from its mother, you need to express your love sufficiently.
It would be good to check the level of motor development."</item>
        <item>"Start saying repeated consonants.
They respond to their own name.
Grasp objects with your thumb and forefinger.
Find a toy under the handkerchief.
It is good to check the excretion cycle and the condition of the stool."</item>
        <item>"He can crawl and stand on his own.
He is very curious and gets angry when toys are taken away.
Imitate other people's actions.
I can hold my mom’s hand and take a step or two.
As you become more assertive, it's easy for you to cry and throw tantrums."</item>
        <item>"I can stand up on my own.
We can walk holding hands.
Grasp small objects with your thumb and index finger.
I like to explore with my hands.
I can hold a cup and drink by myself.
People you see often will recognize you even after a few days.
Adjust baby food according to diarrhea/indigestion"</item>
        <item>"I can distinguish between praise and scolding.
Shows interest in colorful and vivid pictures.
You can play simple ball games.
You can adjust your posture when dressing."</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>